已经完成了。让我们来看看答案。在main activity的菜单排版文件里
Done already. Let's go to the solution. In the menu layout file for the main
也叫做main.xml，添加一个菜单选项
activity, called main.xml, we add another menu item
它总是会在溢出菜单里
that will always be in the overflow menu.
也要在string.xml里定义一个字符串。这个菜单要添加在
We also define the string in the strings.xml file. The menu will be inflated in
main activity里。这样我们就可以操作
the main activity class, so we can handle
这个新添加的菜单选项，通过调用
the map menu item being inflated. By calling
一个叫openPreferredLocationInMap的协助函数
helper method called openPreferredLocationInMap
这个协助函数从SharedPreferences
The helper method reads the users
读取用户的偏好地址信息。然后
preferred location from SharedPreferences. Then we
我们创建一个View Intent。把地址信息放进
create a view intent, indicating it's location
它的数据URI。数据URI的格式可以在通用Intent的文档里找到
in the data URI. The format of the data URI was from the documentation
你还可以添加一个邮编号码作为地址的查询参数
page on common intents. Where you can append a postal code as a query parameter.
最后，我们用这个Intent做参数调用startActivity
Finally, we start an activity with [SOUND] this intent. Note
注意，只有当这个Activity能被成功分解时，我们才开始这个Activity
that we only start the activity, if the activity resolves successfully.